The kettle and the idol
Now then, the second one.
Donkey
Donki
I've already said this flip somewhere.
Don Quijote
I love Don Quijote.
That's right.
What is the charm of Don Quijote?
The charm of Don Quijote is its catchy background music.
What? Seriously?
I think it's wonderful.
And you can create your own original dances on TikTok and so on.
Really?
Yes, it is.
To the music?
Yes. That's why my dream is to dance it in front of Don Quijote in various regions,
Wow, that's cool.
Oh, are you guys really doing that?
I've seen a lot of people from overseas doing it,
It's not so popular in Japan,
I think I mentioned it at night, but in the past, I was told by one of the members, Nao Sakura, that I was like an iconic donkey.
I think she said it in the past, but I think she said it at night too.
My dream was to dance at Donki.
First of all, the catchiness of the background music was appealing.
And the font itself is very attractive.
It certainly makes you want to buy it, doesn't it? The book and the intrigue. The customization.
Doesn't it make you want to buy it?
The book is indeed very handwritten, but so are all the stores.
Donkey, you're right.
That's TikTok, too,
There are videos of the book and the writing process.
Oh, that's the part where he writes?
That's right.
So, I don't know,
I think they probably have a training program when you enter Don Quijote.
I see.
That's it.
That's right. It's just a selfish fantasy.
I want to go on location more.
I want to know.
Let's go together. Kakan-kun.
Yes, that's right. I'm okay with it. Maybe you and Omuro-san should go with Takami-san.
Then we'll do the Don Quixote dance in front of Don Quixote with Reni-chan.
That's a little irresistible.
I'd like to make it happen as soon as possible.
I'm not trying to be funny, but I'd like to see it.
I'll let them know.
I'll let them know. Thank you very much. Please do.
That's how I like donkeys.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm just trying to get deeper into the Don Quijote story.
May I?
You know, sometimes there are places that are combined with supermarkets.
They have a huge variety of meats.
I didn't know that.
You didn't know that?
They have a huge variety of pork, beef, chicken, etc.
But they also have mega mega mega mega mega mega mega mega mega mega mega mega mega mega mega meat for barbecue.
There is also a huge Tupperware container of tongue, and so on.
It's crazy!
Wow!
The meat section is really huge, and now that I've heard about it, I'm really looking forward to the barbecue!
I have an image that Donki seems to like meat.
They have a huge selection of barbecue sets.
They even sell tents!
Like spring tents.
So I guess a lot of people buy those as a set.
I have an image that there's a lot of meat that you can just grill.
I have the image that there are so many of them.
It's not just miscellaneous goods.
but also food
Fresh food
You know, I've never heard of meat being so great.
I've never heard of it.
Really? Well, pay attention.
Yes, I see.
It's a lot of meat.
I see.
Mr. Donkey, I'm glad you can make this presentation.
Please do.
Please let me sing the Donkey theme song.
I'll sing it.
I want to sing.
I'll dance and I'll sing
I want to dance.
With Leni-chan!
Yes, and I'll follow you, too, Takagi.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, we're going to have a bath in a bathtub!
What's this show about?This program is sponsored by
Mr. Pinky
Mr. Wrench
Mr. Ultra Violent Money Man
Mr. Penkey Mr. Penkey Mr. Wrench
Mr. Ultra-violent muscle man
Mr. Cribbon
This page was sent to you courtesy of Mr. Hiroo of Keroro.
Happy!
하삐